aussiepages.com.au 2013-06-01

# Privacy Policy | Classifieds Directory Australia | Business Directory Listings Australia

|   
---  

|    

|    
  
| 

AussiePages Privacy Policy   
  
---  

AussiePages.com.au operates an online business and entertainment directory for Australian and international businesses and or websites. Your inclusion of your business and or website to the directory is conditional upon your acceptance and compliance with these terms and any other specific conditions, notices and disclaimers contained in the website including the " _Privacy Policy_ " and the " _Terms and Condition_ " Please read the Privacy Policy carefully.  

**Advertisements**  
Advertisers or sponsors on our websites may collect information when you view or click on their advertisements. We do not have any control over this data collection. We recommend reading there privacy policy and terms and condition  
   
**Other sites**  
Please note that our website contains links to other websites which are not administered by us. If you click on a link to another website and subsequently leave our website, our Privacy Policy will no longer apply. We suggest that you refer to the privacy policy relating to the other website you are visiting.  
   
**Do we collect any personal information from you?**  
At times we make collect your personal information, however we will not disclose any information collected by you to any third party unless requested by a court of law.   
   
**What do we do with your information?  
**At times we may need to contact you regarding your account, competitions or to update records. All your information is kept safe and away from all employees. Except those who have special clearance for such information.   
   
**IP Collecting  
**We collect your IP address to help limit and protect your information. We will not disclose your IP address to anyone unless requested by a court of law.   

**Email Privacy Policy**  
We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information.   
**     Why did you receive an email from us? **

  1. your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared your email address for the purpose of receiving information in the future ("opt-in"), or 
  2. you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings. 

**How we protect your privacy  
**We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by our system.   
   
**Sharing and Usage**  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone, without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to selected employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.  
   
**How can you stop receiving email from us?**  
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply reply back 'STOP' in the subject line, and you will stop receiving emails from us _this can take up to 48 hours_  

**Why we collect personal information**  
We collect Personal information for a number of reasons, including: 

  * to provide you with our products or services;
  * to administer our relationship with you; 
  * to facilitate the running of trade promotions and other competitions; 
  * to monitor activity on our websites, for the purpose of maintaining the security of those websites; 
  * to compile a databases to enable us to market our goods and services more accurately; 
  * to provide advertisers with information to assist them in their decision making processes and marketing of goods and services. 

**How we collect personal information**  
We primarily collect Personal Information directly from you through written and/or verbal means of communication. However, Personal Information may be collected in a variety of ways, including: 

  * application forms; 
  * competition entry forms; 
  * email; 
  * posted mail; 
  * websites (including in some instances cookies); 
  * online transactions; 
  * public surveys; 
  * business contacts (e.g. contractual documents); and 
  * other forms of written and / or verbal communication. 

We may also collect anonymous information through the use of cookies on our website. Cookies are pieces of information that are stored on your computer's hard disk. Most web-browsers are set to accept cookies but you can set your web-browser to refuse cookies. Cookies themselves do not identify users personally but they do allow the tracking of an Individual's use of a website. Cookies have become commonplace and are used by most websites.  
   
**The type of information we hold about you**   
We only hold information about you that is relevant to our relationship with you. Generally, the Personal Information we hold will include (where relevant) your name, contact details, membership/card/account number/s, records of correspondence, subscription and payment details, type of business and billing statements.   
   
**How we hold your personal information**   
Depending on the circumstances, we may hold Personal Information in hardcopy or electronic form, or both. Generally, we keep hardcopies of all correspondence that we enter into and maintain details about Individuals that we interact with in our electronic database.   
   
**How we secure your personal information**  
We hold all hardcopy and electronic records of personal information in a secure manner to ensure that it is protected from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. Personal information held in electronic form is, wherever practical, password protected and/or encrypted.   
We limit the information that our staff have access to, to help protect your privacy; however there may be times where staff may request specific information about you to help process your request.   

**You may correct your personal information**  
We regularly monitor the quality and accuracy of Personal Information that we maintain and, where practicable, update that information. In addition, you may request that your Personal information be updated at any time  

| 

**Recent Listings**  
  
---  
  
| 

Web Science is a highly skilled provider of all things related to websites and the internet. We create beautiful and highly functional professional websites for any business or niche and we are located close to Parramatta.  

---  
  
With more than 12yrs experience in the wedding industry, Classic Elegance create beautiful images of your wedding day with a personal touch, flexible options and affordable packages starting at $1495.  

Glamorous is a vibrant and youth­ful online busi­ness that prides itself on provid­ing the hot­test fash­ion jew­ellery and hand­bags to our cus­tom­ers through­out Australia. Drawing inspir­a­tion from the latest trends in London, New York, Paris and Tokyo, we strive to provide you wit  

Willco Consulting was founded in 2007 and brings together over 16 years of experience drawing Architectural Plans and dealing with local councils in Sydney, Bathurst, Blue Mountains, ACT, Wollongong and the South Coast.  

Willco Consulting was founded in 2007 and brings together over 16 years of experience drawing Architectural Plans and dealing with local councils in Sydney, Bathurst, Blue Mountains, ACT, Wollongong and the South Coast.  

A huge range of Designer Label Makeup and Cosmetics from Revlon, Loreal, Maybelline, Covergirl, Almay and Rimmel. We also stock brand name Jewellery and Silk Men's Ties from the worlds most famous designers. Best of all we sell all the above items at the cheapest prices in Australia.  

[**PARTY SHUTTLE BUS, PARTY BUS HIRE SYDNEY, CHARTER MINIBUS SYDNEY**](http://www.aussiepages.com.au/PARTY-SHUTTLE-BUS-PARTY-BUS-HIRE-SYDNEY-CHARTER-MINIBUS-SYDNEY.html)  
Welcome to PartyShuttle.com.au 04500 600 55 Delivering You The Safe Way in our 14,21,24 & 42 Seater Party Bus, All our Sydney Party Buses have a great special lighting affects & 1000 Watt sound system to listen to your favourite CD or iPhone (AUX cable) music.  

Lucrative Online Home Business promoting Award Winning and Accredited Personal Leadership Development products for Success Education.  

Best bike servicing shop in Sydney, New South Wales (NSW). Repair, parts, tools, custom builds, bike accessories, bike wheels, & other cycling needs in the Eastern Suburbs & Inner City  

[**Rhinoplasty in Melbourne at Advance Beauty Cosmetic Surgery**](http://www.aussiepages.com.au/Rhinoplasty-in-Melbourne-at-Advance-Beauty-Cosmetic-Surgery.html)  
Avail the low average rhinoplasty cost in Melbourne at Advance Beauty Cosmetic Surgery. The clinic is headed by Dr Ahnsup Kim, a Korean cosmetic surgeon in Australia for 10 years.
